

### **Contact**

**Address** Savar-Dhaka, BD

**Phone** +880 1981663443

Email csesifatshaikh@gmail.com

# **Skills**

- Web design
- Ms word
- Ms excel
- Al Using
- Canva

# Languages

- Bangla
- English

## **Hobbies**

- Travelling
- Cricket
- Cooking

# **MD SIFAT SHAIKH**

### **CSE Student**

### **Profile**

I am a dedicated student with a passion for web design and development. With a year of experience in web design, I aim to create effective and visually engaging solutions that address real-world challenges through innovative thinking.

# **Work Experience**

#### **Junior Web Designer**

Genuity System Li - Dhaka

Aug 2024 - Oct 2024

- Led Web team for Multi vendor Ecommerce Site, Design user engagement by 20% in Three months.
- I also worked on a single vendor ecommerce website myself.
- Have basic experience using AI

#### **MS Office**

Master Computer Institute – Savar, Dhaka May 2021 – Nov 2021

I have hands-on experience using MS Office applications, including Word, Excel, and PowerPoint, for various tasks such as document creation, data analysis, and presentations. My skills in MS Office have allowed me to efficiently manage tasks, streamline workflows, and improve overall productivity

### **Education**

#### **Diploma In Engineering**

shyamoli ideal polytechnic institute – Dhaka 2020 – 2024

#### **HSC**

Redio Colony Model Collage 2023 – 2024